Guide to the Reynolds Price Papers, 1927-2010 and undated, bulk 1956-2006
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Writings Series (RESTRICTED), 1935-2004 and undated, (92 boxes)
  - Writings by Others Subseries (RESTRICTED), 1935-2004 and undated, (16 boxes)
    - Moffatt, Jan E.
      - When I'm Painting, I Don't Have Cancer, 1995 June 27
    - Mofford, Frank
      - Phona, 1993
      - Solo Shoo-shoo, 1993
    - Morgan, Robert (Box WO7)
      - Brave Enemies, 2003, (2 folders)
    - Payne, Peggy
      - Sister India, 1994
    - Peterson, Dwight N.
      - A Gimp's-Eye View of the Healing of the Paralytic in Mark 2:1-2, circa 1997
    - Peterson, Mike
      - A Short and Unhappy Weekend, undated
    - Pollack, Harriet and Suzanne Marrs, eds.
      - Eudora Welty and Politics: Did the Writer Crusade?, 2000
    - Pope, Deborah
      - Mortal World, (Typescript), undated
      - Mortal World, (Advance uncorrected proofs), undated
    - Porter, Joe Ashby
      - Bone Key, 1996
      - St. Silvere's Head, 1981
    - Pratt, Minnie Bruce
      - Poems and statement of plans, 1997 Mar. 4 and undated
    - Price, William, S.
      - My Farewell -- Dripping with Tears, 1950
      - Untitled report, 1935
    - Price, William S., Jr.
      - N.C. v. B.C. West, Jr., 1978
      - John Hope Franklin: a Life of Making History, undated
    - Rambo, Wiley Claude
      - Mint Chip and Plain Vanilla, 1993
    - Randall, Dale B.J.
      - American 'Mairzy' Dottiness, Sir John Fastolf's Secretary, and the 'Law French' of a Caroline Cavalier, 1995
    - Randolph, Leonard
      - Village Dying, circa 1976
    - Robinson, Marilyne
      - Death of Adam, 1998
    - Schiff, James A.
      - Understanding Reynolds Price, 1995, (Folder 1 of 2)
      - Understanding Reynolds Price, 1995, (Folder 2 of 2) (Box WO8)
      - Critical Essays on Reynolds Price, 1996-1997, (3 folders)
    - Sedgwick, Eve Kosofsky
      - A Dialogue on Love, 1999
    - Seymour, James
      - Holy Ghosts and Hidden Histories, 1997
    - Singer, William
      - Eyes: A Gift, 1976
      - Poem A and Poem C, undated
      - Revelation as Grace: A Study of the Twenty-Two Dreams in Reynolds Price's The Surface of Earth, 1977
    - Sink, Alice E.
      - What University Freshmen Have Taught Me About Reynolds Price's Novel, Kate Vaiden, undated
    - Smith, Allen
      - Preacher: The Life of Reverend Helen Gray Crotwell, 1996
    - Smith, Caleb (Box WO9)
      - Monumental, (Typescript), 2001
      - Monumental, (Second draft), 2001
    - Smith, D. Moody
      - Jesus of Nazareth: From Bornkamm to Sanders and Professor Sanders at Duke, undated
      - John As Historian, 2003
      - When Did the Gospels Become Scripture? 2000
    - Smith, Dave
      - The Canoe in the Basement, 1988
      - Cuba Night, 1988
      - In Search of the Real Thing, 1988
      - Southern Crescent, 1988
      - To Isle of Wight, undated
      - Why Southern Poetry May Be a Snipe Hunt, 1988
      - Fate's Kite: Poems, 1992-1995, 1995
      - The Righting Moment: Poems, 1988-1998 undated
      - The Wick of Memory: New and Selected Poems, 1970-2000 1999
    - Smith, Jean Kennedy and George Plimpton
      - Very Special Artists: Chronicles of Courage, 1993
    - Smith, R. T.
      - Brightwood: Poems, 2003
    - Spencer, Elizabeth (Box WO10)
      - Landscapes of the Heart: A Memoir, 1996
    - Spender, Stephen
      - Engaged in Writing, (Typed draft), undated, (2 folders)
      - Engaged in Writing (Typescript), undated
      - Engaged in Writing (Proof), undated, (4 folders)
      - Engaged in Writing (Volume), 1957
      - Engaged in Writing (Price's notes), 1957
      - The Connecting Imagination, 1961 Apr. 1
      - The Fool and the Princess (Bound typescript), undated
      - Journals: 1939-1983, (Folders 1-8 of 13)
    - Spender, Stephen (Box WO11)
      - Journals: 1939-1983, (Folders 9-13 of 13)
      - Schiller's "Mary Stuart," (Handwritten draft), undated
      - Schiller's "Mary Stuart," (Manuscript), undated
      - Schiller's "Mary Stuart," (Typescript), undated
      - Schiller's "Mary Stuart," (Fourth draft), undated
      - Schiller's "Mary Stuart," (Published pages), 1959
      - The Temple, 1960
      - Book Jackets, 1985
      - Poetry, 1960-1983 and undated
      - Essays, undated
    - Stokes, Adrian
      - Vermeer and Degas, undated
    - Stokes, Harry (Box WO12)
      - Untitled work, 1967
    - The Store of Joys: Writers Celebrate the North Carolina Museum of Art's Fiftieth Anniversary, 1995-1996, (2 folders)
    - Styron, William
      - A Lifesketch #1, 1974
      - A Lifesketch #2, 1974
    - Sutherland, John
      - Stephen Spender: The Authorized Biography, 2000, (4 folders)
      - Stephen Spender: The Authorized Biography, (Second draft), undated, (Folders 1-2 of 4)
      - Stephen Spender: The Authorized Biography, (Second draft), undated, (Folders 3-4 of 4) (Box WO13)
    - Tamplin, Ronald
      - The Catechumen, undated
    - Tate, Allen
      - All is Brillig (or ought to be), numbered, limited edition of Tate's last published poem, 1979
    - Tompkins, Jane
      - Let's Get Lost, undated
    - Torgovnick, Marianna
      - Primitive Passions: Men, Women, and the Quest for Ecstasy, 1997
    - Tyler, Anne
      - In Sudden Solitude: A Critical Essay from a Rising Sophomore, 1959
    - Vaughn, Caroline
      - notes on Borrowed Time and career narrative, 1995 Oct. 22
    - Vauthier, Simone
      - "The Circle in the Forest: Fictional Space in A Long and Happy Life," 1974
      - "Reasonable Uses of the Unreasonable: The Supernatural in Reynolds Price's Love and Work," undated
    - Verdelle, A. J.
      - The Good Negress, 1994
    - Verghese, Abraham
      - The Tennis Partner, 1998
    - Voll, Daniel
      - Dear Mr. President, (Typescript), 1992
      - Dear Mr. President, (Second draft), 1992
      - The Flying Saucer Cafe, 1992
      - Moon Child, 1992
      - Riot Baby, 2002
      - To the Shoreline, undated
      - Skin, 1995 (Box WO14)
      - Threat Matrix, 2002
      - Threat Matrix: Episode 104, In Plane Sight, 2003
    - Wagenknecht, Edward
      - Dickens and the Scandalmongers, 1950
    - Wasserman, Harriet
      - Handsome Is: Adventures with Saul Bellow, undated, (2 folders)
    - Welty, Eudora
      - A Flock of Guinea Hens Seen from a Car, 1970
      - One Time, One Place, 1971
      - Place in Fiction, 1955
      - One Writer's Beginnings, (Typescript with notes), undated
      - The Optimist's Daughter, (Galleys with notes), [ 1970?]
      - The Optimist's Daughter (Typescript with notes), 1970, (2 folders)
    - West, James L. W., III
      - Duke, Second Stint, undated
      - Durham and Flatbush, undated
      - Styron at Duke, 1943-44, 1995
      - Styron in Paris, 1995
    - West, John Cameron
      - A Sidebar to 'Esse Quam Videri,' undated
    - Wilbur, Richard
      - Pedestrian Flight, 1981
    - Wilkinson, Alec
      - My Mentor, 2001, (2 folders)
      - A Murder, 1992, (2 folders) (Box WO15)
      - Untitled, 1994
    - Williams, Rowan
      - The Poems of Rowan Williams, 2003
    - Willingham, Dan
      - Untitled, 1996
      - An Untitled Romantic Comedy in Two Acts, 1995
    - Willimon, William H.
      - 'We Work Hard, We Play Hard': A Report for the President and the Provost, and the Vice President of Student Life of Duke University, 1993
      - Tell Me the Story of Jesus, 1995
    - Willrich, Patricia Rowe
      - A Perspective on Wallace Stegner, 1991
      - Watching Through Windows: A Perspective on Anne Tyler, 1992
    - Wilson, Robert
      - Untitled, 1995
    - Yungblut, June
      - The Entered Heart, 1986
    - Miscellaneous writings by indeterminable authors, 1953-1983 and undated
    - Bibliographies, 1974-1983
      - A Bibliography of the Writings of Reynolds Price, by Stuart Wright and James L.W.West:
        - Typescript A, 1979, (2 folders)
        - Typescript B, 1980, (2 folders) (Box WO16)
        - Typescript C, 1981, (2 folders)
        - Typescript D, 1983, (2 folders)
        - Typescript: (Price's copy with holograph corrections, 1983)
      - A Bibliography of the Writings of Reynolds Price, by Stuart Wright and James L. W. West: Proof, 1985
        - Sketches for frontispiece, undated
      - A Selected Bio-Bibliography of Reynolds Price, by Barbara R. Swain, 1974
      - Reynolds Price: A Bibliography, by Clayton Owens (Working draft with corrections by Price), 1976
      - Miscellaneous Bibliographies, 1977-1982
    - Dictionary of Literary Biography
      - Proof for entry on Price for American Short Story Writers Since World War II, Second Series, Vol. 218, 1999
      - Proof for entry on Price for American Novelists Since World War II, Seventh Series, Vol. 278, 2003
- Printed Materials Series, 1944-2004 and undated, (29 boxes)
  Divided into three subseries: Serials, Clippings, and Miscellaneous Printed Materials.
  - Serials Subseries, 1951-2004 and undated, (20 boxes)
    Consists of popular and scholarly serial publications containing work by Price or articles about Price. Arranged chronologically.
    A folder in the inventory cabinet in Research Services contains a list of titles of those serials published through 1992.The folder also contains several lists of selected articles sorted by genre (Interviews, Articles about Price, Short Stories, Reviews of Work by Price, etc.).
    - 1951 Feb.-1963 Summer (Box S1)
    - 1963 Fall-1968 June (Box S2)
    - 1968 Oct.-1970 May (Box S3)
    - 1970 Sept.-1972 (Box S4)
    - 1972-1976 Spring (Box S5)
    - 1976 Spring/Summer-1981 Apr. (Box S6)
    - 1981 May-1984 Jan. (Box S7)
    - 1984 Spring/Summer-1986 Winter/Spring (Box S8)
    - 1986-1988 Summer (Box S9)
    - 1988 Winter-1990 Apr. (Box S10)
    - 1990 May-1990 Dec. (Box S11)
    - 1990 Fall-1991 Spring (Box S12)
    - 1991 Summer-1992 Spring (Box S13)
    - 1992 Spring/Summer-1993 Winter (Box S14)
    - 1993 Winter-1994 Fall (Box S15)
    - 1994-1995 (Box S16)
    - 1995 Winter/Spring-1997 Nov. (Box S17)
    - 1997 Winter-1999 Dec. 6 (Box S18)
    - 1999 Dec. 6-2002 Summer (Box S19)
    - 2002 Fall-2004 Winter and undated (Box S20)
  - Clippings Subseries, 1963-2004 and undated, (2 boxes)
    Clippings chiefly concerning Price and his work, and to a lesser extent his family, friends, and colleagues. Arrangement is as follows: Clippings in Box PC1 consist mostly of reviews, advertisements, and articles regarding specific works by Price and are foldered by title, in order of date of publication. Clippings in Box PC2 are more general articles about or by Price, including interviews, and are arranged chronologically.
    - Reviews of specific works (Box PC1)
      - Blue Calhoun (1992)
      - The Collected Stories (1993)
      - A Whole New Life (1994)
      - The Promise of Rest (1995)
      - The Three Gospels (1996)
      - The Collected Poems (1997)
      - Roxanna Slade (1998)
      - Learning a Trade (1998)
      - Letter to a Man in the Fire (1999)
      - A Perfect Friend (2000)
      - Feasting the Heart (2000)
      - Noble Norfleet (2002)
      - A Serious Way of Wondering (2003)
    - Clippings, chronological sequence, 1963-2004, bulk 1992-2004 and undated, (6 folders) (Box PC2)
  - Miscellaneous Printed Materials Subseries (RESTRICTED), 1944-2004 and undated, (7 boxes)
    Programs, playbills, awards, prospecti, and announcements of teaching and speaking engagements. Arranged alphabetically by type of material and chronologically within each folder.
    - American Academy of Arts and Letters, 1993-2003, (2 folders) (Box MP1)
    - Announcements and programs for author appearances: addresses, conferences, readings, and other engagements, 1962-2004 and undated, (Folders 1-7 of 9)
    - Announcements and programs for author appearances: addresses, conferences, readings, and other engagements, 1962-2004 and undated, (Folders 8-9 of 9) (Box MP2)
    - Announcements and programs for events attended: concerts, plays, services, and other occasions, 1949-2004 and undated, (Folders 1-7 of 9)
    - Announcements and programs for events attended: concerts, plays, services, and other occasions 1949-2004 and undated, (Folders 8-9 of 9) (Box MP3)
    - An Appalachian Summer, 2000
    - Awards and honorary degrees, 1964-2003 and undated, (4 folders)
    - Catalogs and brochures with writings by Price, 1999 and undated
    - Duke University events, 1988-2004 and undated
    - Eudora Welty Foundation, 1999-2004 and undated (Box MP4)
    - Fellowship of Southern Writers, 1989, 1994-1997 and undated
    - Invitations, 1993-2003 and undated
    - James Taylor, 1992-2001, (5 folders)
    - National Book Award Week, 1979 Apr. 23-26
    - Oxford University printed material, 1954-1962 and undated
    - Posters advertising books and lectures, 1982 and 1986
    - Programs and announcements for Price's plays, 1956-2003 and undated, (2 folders)
    - Publications by various authors (alphabetical), 1959-1995 and undated, (Folders 1-3 of 5)
    - Publications by various authors (alphabetical), 1959-1995 and undated, (Folders 4-5 of 5) (Box MP5)
    - Publishers' ads, catalogs, and prospecti, 1966-2000 and undated, (7 folders)
    - Salzberg Seminar in American Studies, 1975-1977 and undated (Box MP6)
    - Spender family printed material, 1959-1977 and undated
    - Teaching and speaking engagements, 1962-1990 and undated
    - Van Cliburn International Piano Competition, 1993-1994, (4 folders)
    - Miscellany, 1944-2001 and undated, (8 folders) (Box MP7)
- Legal and Financial Papers Series (RESTRICTED), 1939-2004 and undated, (5 boxes)
  Consists of publishing agreements and contracts, royalty statements, tax records, papers regarding the William S. Price home, and miscellaneous personal records. Arranged alphabetically in these categories and chronologically within them, with the exception that miscellaneous records are grouped at the end of the series.
  - Publishing agreements and contracts, 1957-2002 and undated, (3 folders) (Box LF1)
  - Royalty statements, 1962-1984, 1992-2004, (6 folders)
  - Tax records, 1964, 1967, (2 folders)
  - Tax records, 1970-1979, (19 folders) (Box LF2)
  - Tax records, 1980-1984, (13 folders) (Box LF3)
  - Tax records, 1985-1990, (8 folders) (Box LF4)
  - William S. and Elizabeth Price, check books, 1954-1965
  - William S. and Elizabeth Price Home, 1939-1969 and undated
  - Miscellaneous legal and financial records, 1950-2003, (Folders 1-2 of 7)
  - Miscellaneous legal and financial records, 1950-2003, (Folders 3-7 of 7) (Box LF5)
- Speeches and Addresses Series (RESTRICTED), 1957-2004 and undated, (1 box)
  Speeches and addresses presented by Price at literary or educational events. Arranged chronologically.
  [RESTRICTED: materials in this series are open for researchers to view but not to duplicate. During Price's lifetime and twenty years thereafter, duplication by any means of materials in this series requires prior written permission from him or his literary executors.]
  - 1957 (Box SA1)
    - Blackburn, William, senior class banquet, Woman's College, May 15
  - 1966
    - The Thing Itself, Duke University
  - 1967
    - The Writer's Role, Twelfth Annual North Carolina Literary Forum, Mar. 16
  - 1968
    - Introduction for prose readings, Library of Congress, Mar.
  - 1970
    - Belhaven College, Jackson, Mississippi, Feb.
  - 1972
    - William Blackburn eulogy, Dec. 8
  - 1973
    - Lecture for the Baylor School, Apr. 22
    - Knowles, John, introduction for, Oct. 28
  - 1974
    - Welty, Eudora, introduction for, Oct. 16
    - Modaressi, Anne Tyler, introduction for, Nov. 13
  - 1975
    - Campus Club Lecture Series, Duke University, Jan. 15
    - Peacock, Phyllis, introduction for, May 7
  - 1976
    - Liberating Journalism: Defining Reality Through Fiction, notes for Duke Fellows in Communication Policy program, Mar. 18-20
  - 1977
    - Salzburg Seminar in American Studies, June 12-July 2
  - 1978
    - Macon Methodist Church, homecoming, Sept. 17
  - 1979
    - Archibald Smith lecture, Apr.
    - To the Chaired Professors, manuscript draft, Oct. 15
  - 1980
    - Joel Jackson's News, Weather, and Sports, draft comment, Oct. 3
  - 1981
    - Spender, Stephen, introduction for, Feb. 2
  - 1983
    - Anderson, Jeffrey, introduction for, Carrboro Art School
  - 1985
    - Truths for Playwrights, Hendrix College, Oct. 18
  - 1986
    - National Book Critics Circle Award, acceptance speech (for Kate Vaiden)
  - 1988
    - Blackburn, William, commemoration of, homecoming weekend, Oct. 21
  - 1989
    - Welty, Eudora, eightieth birthday, Apr. 9
    - Pen-Faulkner reading, Oct. 30
  - 1992
    - Our Half of the Deal, Founder's Day, Dec. 10
  - 1994
    - Clear Pictures premiere (Charles Guggenheim documentary film), Mar. 18
    - Styron, William, introduction for, Nov.
  - 1998
    - Remarks at the awarding of a cookery prize to Ben and Karen Barker, Durham, Sept. 13
  - 1999
    - Oates, Joyce Carol, introduction for, Duke University, Mar. 26
    - A Presentation to the North Caroliniana Society, Apr. 9
    - Letter to a Pair of Trinity College Freshman, as read to the Trinity College Board of Visitors, Apr. 15
    - At an Unveiling, Duke University, Sept. 30
    - An Awful Gift and a Blindness: The Robert Penn Warren Lecture, Nashville, Oct. 8
    - A New Year's Greeting, James Taylor's Millenium Concert in the Raleigh Sports Arena, Dec. 31-2000 Jan. 1
  - 2001
    - Donoghue, Denis, introduction for, Mar. 6
    - Malone, Michael, introduction for, Mar. 8
    - A Serious Way of Wondering, The Peabody Lecture, Harvard Memorial Church, Apr. 21
    - In Long Measure, for W. D. Davies, May 24
    - A Serious Way of Wondering, National Cathedral, Washington, D. C., Sept. 26
  - 2003
    - Spencer Heilema, Mary Elizabeth, eulogy, Jan. 7
    - Keohane, Nan, remarks for a celebratory dinner, Oct. 4
  - 2004
    - Faces From the Flood: Remembering Hurricane Floyd, voiceover script recorded by Price at WUNC-TV, Apr. 12
  - Undated
    - Capra, Frank, introduction of
    - Don Quixote, lecture
    - Milton, John, poetry reading, introduction
    - Unpublishable Fiction
- Interviews Series (RESTRICTED), 1973-2003 and undated, (1 box)
  Interviews with Price regarding his life and work. Includes oral history interview conducted by the Memphis State Oral History Office. Arranged chronologically.
  [RESTRICTED: materials in this series are open for researchers to view but not to duplicate. During Price's lifetime and twenty years thereafter, aduplication by any means of materials in this series requires prior written permission from him or his literary executors.]
  - 1966 and undated: Kaufman, Wallace, A Conversation with Reynolds Price, (5 folders) (Box I1)
  - 1973-1976: Memphis State Oral History Office interview, (10 folders)
  - 1976 Mar. 11: Georges, Gary, A Great Deal More: Une Interview de Reynolds Price
  - 1976: Rooke, Constance, On Women and His Own Work: an Interview with Reynolds Price, (2 folders)
  - 1986 Apr. 9: Miller, Edmond, A Conversation with Reynolds Price
  - 1999 Oct. 26: Smith, Rick R. and Miranda Kossoff, The Life and Times of Reynolds Price: A Literary Lion
  - 2002 Feb. 8: Bush, John, Oak Room Interview: James B. Duke Professor of English Reynolds Price
  - 2003 Mar.: Bedway, Barbara, an e-mail interview for Auburn Seminary's newsletter
  - 1988 and undated: Unattributed interviews
- Personal Papers Series (RESTRICTED), 1927-2004 and undated, (1 box)
  Includes itineraries for Price's trips, drawings by Price, and a day book belonging to Mrs. William S. Price. Arranged alphabetically by topic.
  - Day Book of Mrs. William S. Price, 1940 (Box PP1)
  - Drawings, 1952-1960 and undated
  - Gift lists for complimentary copies of his books, circa 1992-1998
  - Miscellaneous information and notes about writing and career, 1995-2003 and undated
  - Personal itineraries for book tours, readings, and other events, 1971-2002 and undated, (2 folders)
  - Personal itinerary for visit to the Memorial Church, Harvard University, 2001 Apr. 20-23
  - Sketchbook, 1977-1980
  - Statements made at ceremonies for friends, including banquets, funerals, and weddings, 1996-2003
  - Transcript of Bill Moyers' Journal: 'Carter and Country,' 1979
  - Miscellany, 1927-2003 and undated, (2 folders)
    Includes ticket stubs and programs from events attended, handwritten invitations, receipts, drawings, and other items.
- Academic Files Series (RESTRICTED), 1969-2003 and undated, (1 box)
  Documents Price's academic and teaching career. Includes course materials, students' writing, Duke University and Duke University English Department memoranda, and related materials. Arranged alphabetically by topic.
  - Bread on the Waters: Reynolds Price, Teacher, a documentary by Wil Weldon, 1997 (Box AF1)
  - Course materials, 1969-1977 and undated
  - Duke University memoranda and reports, 1994-2004
  - Duke University English Department, 1978, 1992-2004
  - Students--enrollments, proposals, and references, 1993-2003
  - Students' writing, 1990-2003 and undated, (4 folders)
  - William M. Blackburn Fund, 1972-1984 and undated
- Photographic Materials Series (RESTRICTED), 1951-2002 and undated, (1 box)
  Photographs of Price, family members, and various other authors at private events and public ceremonies. Arranged alphabetically by subject.
  - American Rhodes Scholars, class of 1955, forty-fifth reunion, Oxford, 2000 June 25-28 (Box PM1)
  - Authors, 1958, 1974, and undated
  - Class, Narrative Poetry, 1987
  - Clear Pictures (film), 1998 and undated, (2 folders)
  - Cover photographs, 1976 and undated
  - England, 1962
  - Family photographs, circa 1947-1948
  - Lyndhurst Foundation, circa 1994
  - Perkins Library exhibit, 2000, (2 folders)
  - Portraits and publicity photographs, circa 1993-1996
  - Price's high school graduating class, 1951
  - Receipt of Litt. D. Degree from Wake Forest University, 1979 May, (2 folders)
  - Welty, Eudora, 1955, 1973-1985
  - Welty, Eudora: Sixth Annual Eudora Welty Americana Awards, including television transcript, 1979 Aug.
  - Unidentified photographs, 1958-1985, 2001-2002 and undated, (4 folders)
- Audiovisual Materials Series (RESTRICTED), 1968-2003 and undated, (9 boxes)
  Audio and video recordings of Price, mainly at public functions such as readings, awards ceremonies, and interviews. Arranged in subseries by format: Audio Materials Subseries and Video Materials Subseries. Total running time (TRT) is shown in parentheses if known.
  [Originals closed to use. Use copies for most items are available in the collection. Otherwise, Technical Services staff must arrange to have use copy made. Please contact Research Services staff before coming to use the collection.]
  [RESTRICTED: during Price's lifetime and twenty years thereafter, access to or copying of materials in this series requires prior written permission from him or his literary executors.]
  - Audio Materials Subseries, 1968-2000 and undated, bulk 1996-2000
    Recording formats consist of audiocassettes, digital audio tapes, reel to reel tapes. Use copies are available for most recordings; see the sub-groupings for details. Master and use copies for all format groupings are housed together and are listed at the end of the series.
    - Audiocassettes, Originals OR1 - OR21 (CLOSED)
      Interviews, readings, commercial recordings, and radio essays delivered by Price on National Public Radio. Arranged chronologically. Total running time (TRT) is shown in parentheses if known. Use copies are available in Box AV3 for all items.
      - OR1-4. 1973-1975, Memphis State University Oral History Research Office, Southern Writers Project, interviews with Reynolds Price (Box AV1)
        - OR1. 1973 June 18, Interview #1 (TRT unknown)
        - OR2. Circa 1973-1975, Interview #2 (TRT unknown)
        - OR3. 1974 Aug. 20, Interview #3 (TRT unknown)
        - OR4. 1975 June 8, Interview #4 (TRT unknown)